嗯 嗯 嗯
Mm, mm, mm.
这蛋糕太好吃了
This cake is amazing. Mm.
天啊 去开个房间吃吧
My God, get a room.
我可以跟这蛋糕闻房间
Mm. I would get a room with this cake.
我想我会和这块蛋糕 有一段很甜蜜的时光
I think I could show this cake a good time.
如果一定要选择的话 你们会放弃食物还是性爱？
If you had to, what would you give up, food or sex?
性爱
Sex.
说真的 你回答得也太快了吧？
Seriously, answer faster.
不好意思 亲爱的
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
但是我刚才说的性爱 并不是指和你在一起的性爱
No, when she said "sex," I wasn't thinking about sex with you, heh.
这像个巨大的拥抱一样温暖
It's like a giant hug.
罗斯 你呢？你会放弃哪一样 性爱还是食物？
Ross, how about you? Which would you give up, sex or food?
- 食物    - 如果是恐龙或性爱呢？
- Food.     - Okay, how about, um, sex or dinosaurs?
老天啊 这真是个困难的选择
Oh, my God, it's like Sophie's Choice.
天啊
Oh, God.
乔伊 你会放弃什么？性爱还是食物？
What about you, Joe? What would you give up, sex or food?
额 额
Uh... Ooh... Uh...
不知道 这太难取舍了
I don't know, it's too hard.
不行 你必须选择一个
No, you gotta pick one.
食物 不 性爱
Uh, food. No, sex.
食物 性爱 食物 性… 不知道 天啊 我两个都要
Food. Sex. Food. Sex... I don't know. Oh, God, I want both.
我要面包夹女人
I want... I want girls on bread.
- 你一定要看看艾玛的照片   - 好可爱
- You gotta see these pictures of Emma.     - Oh, how cute.
- 她像个洋娃娃似的   - 不 那是个洋娃娃
- Oh, she looks just like a little doll.     - Oh, no, that is a doll.
感谢神 因为我觉得那看起来有点吓人
Oh, thank God, because that thing's really creepy.
是啊
Yeah.
看 钱德在那里
Look, there's Chandler.
那个金发女郎是谁？她很漂亮
Oh, who's the blond? She's pretty.
他有外遇了
He's having an affair.
他才不是有外遇呢
He is not having an affair.
我的感觉是很准的
I'm always right about these things.
才怪 上星期你以为罗斯想杀了你
No, you're not. Last week, you thought Ross was trying to kill you.
对不起 我很难相信 有人会说那么无聊的故事
Well, sorry, but it's hard to believe that anyone would tell a story that dull...
就只为了说故事而已
...just to tell it.
他们之间一定有些什么
There's something going on with them.
看 他们一起上车了
Look. He's getting into the car with her.
那并不代表什么
Oh, that doesn't mean anything.
是吗？我们走着瞧
Oh, yeah? Well, let's see.
哈？
Huh?
- 趴低点   - 噢
- Okay, duck down.    - Oh.
- 喂？ - 钱德 我是菲比
- Hello?     - Oh, hi. It's Phoebe.
我知道摩妮卡今天要上班
Um, I know that Monica is working today...
所以我想问你要不要 跟我和瑞秋一起去看电影
...so I was wondering if you wanted to come to the movies with me and Rachel.
嗯 我也要去上班 对 我一整天都会在公司
Oh, uh, I have to work too. Yeah, I'm stuck here at the office all day.
太可惜了 你不能去看电影
Uh, well, it's a shame that you'll miss the movie...
因为我们打算看《王牌大骗子》
...because we were gonna see, you know, either, um, Liar Liar or, um...
《终极背叛》或是《金玉盟》
...Betrayal or An Affair to Remember.
那都是些老片子
Those are all really old.
好 那也许我们会去看…
Okay, then maybe it'll be, um...
猪头 我的车咧？
Dude, Where's My Car?
- 什么？ - 他们在车子里
- What?     - They're in a car.
好了 晚点再聊 再见
Okay. Well, talk to you later, okay? Bye.
天啊
Jeez.
快 我们得拦辆计程车跟踪他们
Okay, quick. We gotta find a cab and follow them.
好 我先去拿我的夜视镜和电击枪
Oh, yeah, okay.
好 我先去拿 我的夜视镜和电击枪
Let me just grab my night-vision goggles and my stun gun. Heh.
我这儿有
I got them.
- 你好   - 你好 甜心
- Hey.     - Hey. Hi, sweetie.
你身上有香水和烟的味道
Hey, you smell like perfume and cigarettes.
- 我今天一整天都和南西在车里   - 南西不抽烟
- I was in the car with Nancy.     - Nancy doesn't smoke.
至少那香水不是我的 这点你应该心存成激
Well, at least the perfume's not mine. Be thankful for that.
你认为那房子怎么样？
So... What did you think of the house?
那是我们梦寐以求的房子
It's everything we've been looking for.
可不是吗？那漂亮的护墙饰条…
Isn't it? And what about the amazing wainscoting...
冠顶饰和阁楼的老虎窗呢？
...the crown molding and the dormer windows in the attic?
还有歪歪曲曲和斜来斜去的？
And the wiggle woms and the zip zorps.
你刚刚说什么？
What were the things you said?
- 你喜欢那个大院子吗？ - 还有主卧房里的壁炉
- Don't you love the huge yard?     - The fireplace in the bedroom.
南西说这个价钱非常优惠
And Nancy said it's really underpriced...
因为那家伙丢了工作 不得不搬去跟父母住
...because the guy lost his job and has to move in with his parents!
看你善良贴心的样子
This is bringing out a lovely color in you.
你觉得我们应该买吗？
So do you think we should get it?
不知道 你觉得呢？
I don't know. What do you think?
- 我觉得我们应该买   - 我也是
- I think we should.     - I do too.
- 这是件大事   - 对啊
- This is huge.     - I know.
你现在有多想抽烟？
How bad do you wanna smoke now?
我不了解你的意思 你这根巨大 会说话的香烟
I don't know what you mean, giant, talking cigarette.
我正在南西车上的时候 菲比打电话来
Phoebe called as I was getting into Nancy's car.
如果她问起 就说我一天都在工作
If she asks you, I was at work all day.
了解 我们什么时候告诉他们？
Got you. When do we tell them?
先别说 等完全确定再说 不必现在就让大家难过
We don't. Not until it's 100 percent. Why upset everybody over nothing?
对
Okay. Right.
- 天啊 这会很难开口   - 我知道 祝你好运
- Oh, my God, that is gonna be so hard.     - I know. Good luck with it.
钱德不是那种会搞外遇的人
I just can't see Chandler cheating.
我告诉你们 我们一路跟踪到 西彻斯特的一栋房子
I'm telling you guys, we followed them out to a house in Westchester.
他们在里面持了有45分钟 出来时似乎很快乐
They went in for 45 minutes, and then they came out looking pretty happy.
- 钱德？ - 嗯
- Chandler?     - Mm-hm.
45分钟？
Forty-five minutes?
肯定有什么地方不对劲
Well, something's not right.
我不敢相信 他会这样对持摩妮卡
I can't believe he'd do this to Monica.
是啊 而且他们就快有小孩了
I know, and with the baby coming?
- 我们该告诉她吗？ - 不知道
- So should we tell her?     - I don't know.
菲比 如果我们看到麦克 跟别的女人在一起 你会想知道吗？
If one of us saw Mike with another woman, would you want us to tell you?
怎么？你看到他跟谁在一起了？
Why? Who'd you see him with?
- 没有 我只在假设…   - 告诉我你知道什么
- No one. I'm just saying if we did...     - Tell me what you know!
没有 没事 麦克是个好男人 我只是假设
No one. Nothing. Mike's a great guy. It was hypothetical.
好吧 他是个好男人
All right. He is a good guy.
你说的对 他不会搞外遇的
You're right. He wouldn't cheat.
如果我真看到 他和另一个女人在一起…
If I did see him with someone, there's no way I...
你看到他跟谁在一起了？
Who did you see him with?
你们看看她有多开心啊
Oh, look at her. So happy.
要是有更小的吸尘器来清理这个 该有多好
If only there were a smaller one to clean this one.
钱德在吗？
Hey, is, uh... Is Chandler here?
不在 他去买晚餐了 发生了什么事吗？
No, he's picking up dinner. Why, what's up?
呃…
Well...
不管发生什么事 我们都在你身边支持你 我们爱你
Look, whatever happens, we're here for you and we love you.
- 好的   - 我们认为钱德可能有外遇
- All right.     - Chandler might be having an affair.
- 什么？ - 菲比和我今天看见钱德…
- What?      - Phoebe and I saw Chandler...
跟一个金发女郎在街上
...with a blond woman today outside on the street.
我们跟踪他们 到一所位于西彻斯特的房子
And then we followed them to a house in Westchester.
他们一起进去里面 我很遗憾
They went in together. I'm so sorry.
我的天…那太糟糕了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, that's awful.
你们觉得那房子怎么样？
What did you think of the house?
什么？
What?
摩妮卡 你了解 我们刚才说的话吧？
Monica, you understand what we're saying, right?
了解 当然了解 我是非常震惊
Yeah. Sure. I mean, I'm devastated, obviously.
你们觉得那边的环境温不温暖？
Did you think the neighborhood was homey?
- 嘿   - 你这狗杂种
- Hey.     - You son of a bitch.
是我的问题 还是 这袒打招呼的方式越来越糟了？
Is it me, or have the greetings gone downhill around here?
菲比和瑞秋 今天看到你和南西在一起
Phoebe and Rachel saw you with Nancy today.
他们以为你和她有一腿
And, um, they think you're having an affair.
- 南西是谁？ - 到底是怎么回事？
- Who's Nancy?     - What's going on?
额
Uh...
好吧…
Okay, uh...
你们大家最好坐下来
All right, you better sit down.
- 这是件大事   - 对
- This is... This is pretty big.     - Yeah.
我没有外遇
I'm not having an affair.
南西是我们的房地产经纪人
Nancy is our realtor.
我就知道他不可能 跟个女人在一起45分钟
I knew he couldn't be with a woman for 45 minutes.
你们为什么要请房地产经纪人？
Why do you have a realtor?
最近都是她带我们 去看住宅区的房子
Um, she's been showing us houses outside of the city.
- 什么？ - 你说真的吗？
- What?     - Are you serious?
当我们知道会有小孩之后…
When we found out that we were gonna get this baby...
钱德和我讨论后决定 我们不想在市区抚养小孩
...Chandler and I decided we didn't wanna raise a kid in the city.
所以你们要搬走？
So you're... So you're gonna move?
我的天
Oh, my God.
这种事我们该投票解决吧？
Shouldn't we all vote on stuff like this?
在市区里带小孩有什么不妥吗？
What is wrong with raising a kid in the city?
我这么做 罗斯也这么做
I'm doing it. Ross is doing it.
莎拉洁西卡帕克也是
Sarah Jessica Parker is doing it.
你们这么做很好啊 但是我们想要有院子和秋千
And that's great for you guys, but we want a lawn and a swing set.
一条孩子们能骑脚踏车的街…
A street where our kids can ride their bikes...
也许还会有冰淇淋车经过
...and maybe an ice-cream truck can go by.
所以你们想在50年代买房子
So you wanna buy a house in the '50s.
你们有想过会失去的东西吗？
Have you thought about what you're giving up?
你们不能搬出市区 要是…
You can't move out of the city. What if...?
要是你们凌晨5点 想吃中国菜怎么办？
What if you want Chinese food at 5 a. M?
或者想买下雨就会停的假劳力士时 怎么办？
Or a fake Rolex that breaks as soon as it rains?
还是想电召亚裔妓女时怎么办？
Or an Asian hooker sent right to your door?
这么说吧 如果你们想看房子 没问题
You know what? If you want to look for a house, that's okay.
不…有问题 别听他的 小心我扁你
No. No, it's not. Don't listen to him. I'm gonna thump you.
没问题 因为他们得先追寻他们的梦想
It's okay, because they have to get it out of their system.
但是你们会发现 这里才是你们真正想住的地方
Okay? But you're gonna realize this is the only place you wanna be.
其实…
Actually...
我们已经找到梦寐以求的房子了
...we already found a house we love.
- 什么？ - 大约一小时前 我们开出了价码
- What?     - About an hour ago, we made an offer.
我敢打赌 你们现在宁可是我有外遇
Bet you wish I was having an affair now, huh?
- 你们已经出价了？ - 那房子真的很好
- You put an offer on a house?     - It's so sweet.
真的 那里有个很大的院子 直通到一条小溪
It really is. It has this big yard that leads down to this stream.
还有很多老枫树
And then there's these old maple trees.
又是大自然 你们自以为是水獭吗？
Oh, again with the nature. What are you, beavers?
我知道你们一时难以接受 我们也非常抱歉
Look, I know this is really hard, and we're really sorry.
不是因为我不敲门 就跑过来拿你们的东西吃吧？
Is this because I come over here without knocking and eat your food?
我可以不要那样
Because I can stop doing that.
我真的可以改
I really, really think I can.
乔伊 你知道 那不是我们要搬走的原因
You know that's not the reason, Joe.
我想如果你们看到那里 就会明白的
I think if you saw it, you'd understand.
你们去看过 那里很美 不是吗？
You guys were there. It's beautiful, isn't it?
- 是啊 的确很美   - 你在做什么？
- Yeah, it is.     - What the hell are you doing?
那里是不错 今天在那里的时候 我心里想的是
Well, it is, all right? When we were out there today, all I kept thinking was:
"我不敢相信 钱德居然做得出这种事
"I can't believe Chandler is screwing this woman...
但是 这真是个居住的好地方 "
...but, man, this would be a nice place to live."
是没错 但是这里也是
Yeah, but so is this.
对啊 如果你们搬过去 就要搬离这里
Yeah. I mean, if you move there, you have to leave here.
你们怎么可以离开这个地方？
I mean, how can you leave this place?
老爸 拜托你听我说
Come on, Daddy, listen to me!
我终其一生 大家都告诉我 "你是鞋子
It's like all of my life, everyone's always told me, "You're a shoe!
你是鞋子 你是鞋子  你是鞋子 "
You're a shoe! You're a shoe! You're a shoe!"
今天我突然想到 "如果我不想当鞋子呢？
Then today I stopped and said, "What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
如果我想当皮包？
What if I wanna be a purse? You know?
或是帽子呢？"
Or a hat?"
我不是要你买帽子给我 我只是说我是帽…
I don't want you to buy me a hat, I am a hat.
我只是打个比方 老爸
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
我可以了解他哪里搞不懂
You can see where he'd have trouble.
也许我就持在摩妮卡这里
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
我想她待在摩妮卡这里 是既成的事实
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.
你的钱就是我的 葛林
Your money's mine, Green.
你的拉链没拉 盖勒
Your fly's open, Geller.
你们知道我刚发现了什么吗？
You know what I just realized?
"扑克牌"头个字母换上J 就是"鬼牌"
"Joker" is "poker" with a "J."
那是巧合吗？
Coincidence?
"巧合"头个字母换上C 就是"绝对不巧"
Hey, that's "jo-incidence" with a "C."
看 奇丑的裸男点了一堆蜡烛
Ooh, look. Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
哦
Ooh.
啊
Oh!
那一定很痛
Ooh. That had to hurt.
这也是你们的威 恩节
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving too.
除了看球赛 也可以过来帮忙
You know, instead of watching football, you could help.
我们知道
[IN UNISON] We know.
瑞秋 你要把这些绵绵糖 摆成一个同心圆
Rachel, you wanna put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
不 摩妮卡 是你要把它们摆成个同心圆
No, you wanna put them in concentric circles.
这是我要做的
I want to do this.
每年都一样
Every year.
我被卡住了
It's stuck.
呃…
Well...
小心阶梯 你是怎么把头塞进去的？
Step. How did it get on?
我戴上去是为了吓钱德
I put it on to scare Chandler.
我的天 摩妮卡看到会抓狂的
Oh, my God! Monica's gonna totally freak out.
还有 这里面臭得要命
Plus, it smells really bad in here.
当然臭 你的头 可是卡在火鸡的屁股里
Of course it smells bad. You have your head inside a turkey's ass.
哦 哦 摩妮卡
Ooh, ooh. Monica.
哦
Ooh.
火鸡拿来了吗？我的天 我的天
Did you get the turkey...? Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
那是谁？
Who is that?
我是乔伊
It's Joey.
我知道了
I got it.
如果我们赢 他们就得把那只公鸡弄走
How about if we win, they have to get rid of the rooster.
那太有趣了
Ooh, that's interesting.
如果你们赢…
If you win...
我们就放弃那只鸡
...we give up the bird. - Aah!
但是 如果我们赢了…
But if we win...
我们要你们住的地方
...we get your apartment.
噢
Ooh!
- 官为定   - 什么？
- Deal!     - What?
摩妮卡当曲棍球守门员时的绰号？
"What was Monica's nickname when she was a field-hockey goalie?"
- 大胖守门员   - 正确
- Big Fat Goalie.     - Correct.
瑞秋宣称她最喜欢的电影是？
"Rachel claims this is her favorite movie."
- 《危险关系》   - 是的
- Dangerous Liaisons.   - Correct.
- 其实她最喜爱的电影是？ - 《老板渡假去》
- "Her actual favorite is?" Correct.      - Weekend at Bernie's.
摩妮卡将她的毛巾分类 共有几个种类？
"Monica categorizes her towels. How many categories are there?"
- 日用   - 精美
- Okay, everyday use.     - Fancy.
- 客人用   - 精美客用
- Guest.      - Fancy guest.
- 还有两秒   - 十一种？
- Two seconds.     - Uh, 11?
十一种 太难以置信了 十一种是正确答案
Eleven. Unbelievable. Eleven is correct.
- 太棒了   - 哈哈
- Yes!     - Ha-ha-ha.
钱德第一次摸女孩子胸部是几岁？
"Chandler was how old when he first touched a girl's breast?"
- 14岁？ - 错 19岁
- Fourteen?     - No, 19.
谢了 兄弟
Thanks, man.
乔伊有个幻想的童年朋友
"Joey had an imaginary childhood friend.
- 他的名字是？ - 莫利斯
- His name was?"     - Maurice.
- 他的职业是？ - 太空牛仔
- "His profession was?"     - Space cowboy!
正确
Correct.
钱德宾的职业是？
"What is Chandler Bing's job?"
哦
Oh.
天啊
Oh, gosh.
还有十秒 这题答错就输了
Ten seconds. You need this or you lose.
好像是跟传输有关的
It has something to do with transponding.
他是个传输人
Oh! Oh! He's a transponster.
根本没有那种东西
That's not even a word!
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 我的天啊   - 不要啊
- Oh, my God.     - No!
哇哦
Whoo!
你们知道吗？你们是卑鄙刻薄的小人
You know what? You are mean boys who are just being mean.
别把气出在我们身上 没人逼你越赌越大
Hey, don't get mad at us. No one forced you to raise the stakes.
不对 是她逼我的
That is not true. She did. She forced me.
你如果没答错问题 我们就不用搬家了
We'd still be here if you hadn't got the question wrong.
那是个愚蠢又不公平的问题
Well, it was a stupid, unfair question!
别怪问题
Don't blame the questions!
别在我们的公寓里乱吼
Would you all stop yelling in our apartment?
把我们的快乐搬家日都毁了
You are ruining moving day for us.
钱德
Chandler!
钱德 我从窗户 看到你在做什么了
Chandler, I saw what you were doing through the window.
我看见你在对我妹妹做什么 你给我出来
I saw what you were doing to my sister. Now, get out here!
听着 我们在一起 度过美好的时光
Well, listen, we had a good run.
多久？大概有4 5个月吧？
You know? What was it? Four, five months?
那比大多数人在一起的时间都久
That's more than most people have in a lifetime.
所以再会了 保重 再见
So goodbye, take care, bye-bye then.
罗斯 发生了什么事  哥？
Hey, Ross. What's up, bro?
你们到底在搞什么？
What the hell are you doing?
喂 发生了什么事？
Hey, what's going on?
我想罗斯知道我和摩妮卡的事了
Well, I think... I think Ross knows about me and Monica.
老兄 怎么当着他的面说这些？
Dude, he's right there.
我以为你是我最好的朋友 她是我的妹妹
I thought you were my best friend. This is my sister.
我最好的朋友跟我妹妹 我简直不敢相信
My best friend and my sister. I cannot believe this.
我们不是玩玩而已 我爱她
We're not just messing around. I love her.
我爱上她了
Okay? I'm in love with her.
我很抱歉 你以这种方式发现
I'm so sorry that you had to find out this way.
抱歉 但这是真的 我也爱他
I'm sorry, but it's true. I love him too.
我最好的朋友和我妹妹
My best friend and my sister.
我简直不敢相信
I cannot believe this.
这是你最后一箱衣服
This is the last box of your clothes.
我要贴上 "你到底在想什么？"的标签
I'm just gonna label it "What were you thinking?"
好笑的是 我本来要到对面 在钱德身上写这句话
Funny, I was just gonna go across the hall and write that on Chandler.
两位小姐 我不想把事情越弄越糟 但是…
Okay, you guys, I don't mean to make things worse, but...
我不想和瑞秋住在一起了
...I don't wanna live with Rachel anymore.
- 什么？ - 你们对对方太刻薄了
- What?      - You're just so mean to each other.
我不想跟瑞秋最后闹得不欢而散 我还是很喜欢你
And I don't wanna end up like that with Rachel. I still like you.
菲比 没关系 因为我不搬了
Well, Phoebe, that's fine because I'm not moving.
菲比 你得跟她一起住
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Phoebe, you gotta take her.
我是说过一些她的坏话…
I know I said some bad stuff...
但是瑞秋有一些优点 足以让她成为个好室友
...but Rachel does have some qualities that make her a good roommate.
她把她觉得我会喜欢的…
She gets tons of catalogs...
商品目录页折起来
...and, um, she'll fold down the pages of the things she thinks I'd like.
- 还有呢？ - 额
- What else?     - Uh...
我洗澡的时候…
When I take a shower...
她会在镜子上留言给我
...she leaves me little notes on the mirror.
我会 我会那么做
Yeah, I do. I do do that.
很好 我喜欢在洗手间里读点东西
That's nice. I like having things to read in the bathroom.
我在沙发上 看书看到睡着的时候…
When I fall asleep on the couch after reading...
她会帮我盖被子
...she covers me over with a blanket.
你知道的 我不想让你着凉了
Well, you know, I don't want you to be cold.
当我告诉她 我要跟钱德一起住的时候…
And when I told her I was gonna move in with Chandler...
她真的很支持我
...she was really supportive.
你太棒了
[SOBBING] You were so great.
你让一切变得那么容易
You made it so easy.
现在你要离开了
And now you have to leave.
而我得和男生住在一起
And I have to live with a boy!
嘿
Hey.
- 她真的走了   - 我知道
- She really left.     - I know.
- 谢谢你   - 没什么 室友
- Thank you.     - No problem, roomie.
- 我能问你一个问题吗？ - 当然
- Can I ask you a question?      - Sure.
那只狗在这里做什么？
What the hell is that dog doing here?
- 我要向大家敬个酒   - 嗯
- A little toast here. Ding, ding, ding.     - Mm.
我知道这并不是你们 计划中的感 惑节
This isn't exactly the kind of Thanksgiving you planned...
但对我来说这一切真的太棒了
...but for me this has been really great, you know?
我想是因为没有牵涉到离婚…
I think because it didn't involve divorce...
或是喷射性呕吐
...or projectile vomiting.
我还在想 如果你去了维尔…
I was just thinking, if you'd gone to Vail...
或是如果你们和家人在一起 如果你没有…
...or if you guys had been with your family, or if you didn't have...
梅毒的问题
...syphilis and stuff...
我们就不会聚在一起
...we wouldn't be all together, you know?
我想我要说的是…
So I guess what I'm trying to say...
我非常感谢 你们的感恩节计划全泡汤了
...is that I'm very thankful that all of your Thanksgivings sucked.
太成人了
That's so sweet.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嗯
Mm.
敬糟糕的耶诞节
And hey, here's to a lousy Christmas.
和不快乐的新年
And a crappy New Year.
干杯 干杯
Hear, hear.
你们不能搬 你们就是不能搬走
You can't move. You just... You just can't.
瑞秋说的对 你们是属于这里的
Rachel's right. This is where you guys belong.
你们不能搬到西彻斯特 那是彻斯特区里最糟糕的
You don't wanna live in Westchester. That's the worst of the Chesters.
有时候我一个人在家里 我往这里看…
You know, sometimes when I'm alone in my apartment, I look over here...
你们会在这里吃晚餐…
...and you guys are just having dinner...
或看电视之类的
...or watching TV or something...
那会让我有点温馨的感觉
...but it makes me feel better.
以后我再往这里看 我会看到谁呢？
And now when I look over, who am I gonna see?
高特立家还是杨家？
The Gottliebs? The Yangs?
他们不会让我感觉温馨
They don't make me feel so good.
是啊 所以别搬了 就留下来吧
Yeah. So don't move, okay? Just stay here...
晚上别忘记拉窗帘就行了   - 你…
...and maybe close your blinds at night.     - Hey.
喂？
Hello?
是南西 他们对我们的价码做出答覆了
It's Nancy. They responded to our offer.
然后呢？
And?
好…
Yeah...
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
他们没兴趣
They passed.
他们说一毛也不愿意降
They said they won't go a penny under the asking price.
- 我们负担不起那价格   - 我知道
- We can't afford that.     - I know.
好了 如你们所愿了
Well, there you go.
真抱歉
I'm really sorry, you guys.
我也很抱歉 我更抱歉在电话来之前…
Yeah, I'm sorry too. I'm even more sorry that phone call didn't come...
就说出从窗户看过来的事情
...before I told you about looking through the window.
我们还是让你们独处一阵子吧
Yeah. Well, we're gonna let you be alone.
- 你们没事吧？ - 我们会没事的
- You gonna be okay?     - Yeah, we'll be okay.
我爱你们
Love you guys.
很抱歉 之前没有支持你们
You know, I'm really sorry I wasn't more supportive before.
没关系 我们能理解
That's okay. We understand.
对了 关于这个南西…
Yeah, and about this Nancy...
如果你没跟她上床的话 能不能让我上？
If you're not sleeping with her, should I?
我知道我们还会找到其他房子 但是我…
I know there'll be other houses, but I just, uh...
- 我太爱那栋房子了   - 是啊
- I loved that one so much.     - Yeah.
所以得到那栋房子是天大的喜事
Well, it's a good thing we got it then.
- 什么？ - 我们买到那栋房子了
- What?     - We got the house.
- 我的天   - 我不想当着他们的面告诉你
- Oh, my God.     - I didn't wanna tell you in front of them.
我们买到了  我们买到那栋房子了？
We got it? We got the house?
- 我们要买房子了   - 啊
- We're getting a house. - Oh!
嗯
Mm.
- 我们要买房子了     - 还要有小孩了
- We're getting a house.     - And a baby.
我们长大了
We're growing up.
是啊
We sure are.
谁去跟他们说呢？
Who's gonna tell them?
- 不是我   - 不是我 可恶
- Not it.     - Not it. Damn it!
- 瑞秋 这是给你的   - 哈
- And, Rachel, this is yours.     - Aah!
这是为了什么？
Why? What are these for?
- 你会知道的   - 大家都打开来看看吧
- You'll see.     - All right, everybody open them.
这好美
Oh, wow, this is so beautiful.
这个我在店里就看上了
Oh, these are the ones I was looking at in the store.
- 我知道   - 我好喜欢
- I know.    - Oh, I love this.
肉丸潜水艇三明治
A meatball sub.
谢谢
Thanks.
说真的 你们怎么了？为什么送我们这些礼物？
Seriously, guys, what's going on? What are these for?
先前不知道该怎么跟你们说
Well, I didn't know how to tell you before...
但是我们买到那房子了   - 请享用
...but we got the house.     - Enjoy.
他们刚刚说什么？
What did they say?